KAMLESH PATIL

Contact

Email: patilkamlesh1811@gmail.com

LinkedIn: iamkamlesh18
GitHub: iamkamlesh18
CV Web: Portfolio Website

Skills

- React
- Angular
- JavaScript
- Node.js
- Python
- SQL & MongoDB
- HTML & CSS
- Agile & Scrum

Certifications

- Agile Software Development
- Responsive Web Design
- Pluralsight -Microsoft Azure Services and Concepts
- GitHub Fundamentals
- Programming with JavaScript

Software and Tools

- VS Code
- My SQL
- Git & GitHub
- Jenkins
- Jira
- Postman

Profile

Software Engineer with the 3 year of industry experience in developing a finest and scalable software application. Strong technical skills in React, Angular, JavaScript, and SQL database. Seeking career opportunities in Full Stack Web Development and always willing to learn new technologies.

Experience

Capgemini – Software Engineer

Sept 2021 - Present

Project: Fleet Management Application - (May 2023 - Present)

Description:

- Developed an automotive fleet management application.
- Created efficient UI components and conducted unit testing.
- Identified and rectified bugs in both frontend and backend components.
- Implemented effective solutions for reported issues.

Project: Loan Application - (Jul 2022 - May 2023)

Description:

- Developed and designed efficient APIs and UIs for Loan Application
- Collaborated with team members to identify and resolve software bugs.
- Provided weekly project updates and maintained JIRA for tracking.
- Delivered high-quality solutions on time.

Project: Progress Plus - (Sept 2021 - Jun 2022)

Description:

- Developed an introductory portal for new joiners.
- Provided essential resources for employees throughout their tenure.
- Ensured seamless access to resources and information.
- Delivered project on time and met all client requirements and expectations.

Education

BE(Mechanical Engineering)

R.C. Patel Institute of Technology Shirpur,2019

Smt. S.S.Patil Institute of Technology Chopda, 2016